You want to make sure that you always apply your wax in the same direction the hair grows.
The hair will not be removed with the wax if you don't do it in this manner.
So I'm going, the hair grows down, and it's, sometimes facial hair tends to grow in several directions.
So if this hair grows in the direction then go this way.
If this hair grows in this direction, then go that way and separate your sections.
But make sure you always apply in the way the hair grows, in the direction the hair is growing.
It's growing this way, I'm applying this way.
Hard wax.
Remember we're going to put it on nice and thick so we have something to grab a hold of.
And then I'm going to remove against the direction of the hair growth.
Perfect.
This is a good little secret tip.
If you have wax that you've previously removed, take that and reapply it to the wax the next section that you're ready to take off, because it gives you like a handle, something to grab a hold of and remove that wax.
Wax sticks to wax, so you can go through and dab that on any little pieces that might be left and remove those wax.
So remember, apply with the growth, remove against the growth.